taggify.net 2018-11-06

# Taggify, Connecting brands with people.

This is our official Privacy Policy which forms part of your legal agreement with us UNDER OUR TERMS OF USE.

**CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY**

We reserve the right, in our sole discretion, to modify, add or delete provisions of this Privacy Policy at any time. We will post the effective date of any change at the top of this Privacy Policy. Your use of our Digital Property after the effective date of any such modification means you accept and agree to be bound by the Privacy Policy, as modified. We urge you to come back to this digital page and review this Privacy Policy regularly so that you remain aware of the terms and conditions that apply to you.

**COLLECTING PERSONAL INFORMATION**

**At the moment Taggify is NOT collecting Personal Information.** In case of any collection, TAGGIFY won't include personal information such as your, postal address (zipcode), email, and telephone number. The information we may collect is non-personal and may include: IP Address, Web Browser, Browser Language and ISP.   
Click here to opt-out.

**HOW WE USE INFORMATION**

We will use information we collect or obtain when you use our Platform as described in this Privacy Policy or as otherwise disclosed at the time of collection, to:

  * Conduct internal research;
  * Operate and administer our Platform;
  * Ensure compliance with our Terms of Use;
  * Respond to your requests for products, services, and/or information;and
  * Communicate with you about TAGGIFY products, services, events, promotions, and other items we believe will be of interest to you;

**ADVERTISERS**

In the course of serving advertisements to our Website, our operational service provider may use cookies and other technologies.

**INFORMATION SHARING**

We do not share Personal Information to anyone.

**SECURITY**

As you may appreciate, the Internet is a public network and we cannot guarantee that communications between you and TAGGIFY or others to, through, or from our Digital Property, will be free from unauthorized access or interference by third parties. By using our Digital Property, you are agreeing to assume this risk and any and all responsibility and liability that may arise. We have put in place reasonable procedures to help safeguard information and we limit access to your Personal Information to only those employees who need access in order to perform their duties.

**CONTACT US**

For questions relating to privacy, we can be contacted at: support@taggify.net or +54 11 2076-3500 or by mail, proper postage prepaid, at TAGGIFY S.A., CABRERA 6061, 8° Floor, BUENOS AIRES, 1427, ARGENTINA, Attention: Privacy Administrator
